Notes for designing the poster

Low Poly

AI+PS required

Find a picture first

Then go to the Behance to get the inspirations

Start to draw the Poly in the AI

And then do the poster design in PS

Adobe Typekit-to get the right font

One word to describe the goal

After the designing, we need to set up a poster with margins, like .25inches with the ruler tool

Poster:
Flyer:
Advertising fee: 200$

Do the landscape instead of animal and people

Declare the reason why the poster is like the

The concept-